We created the today layout so why doesn't it show
up? The reason is because we're using a simple CursorAdapter. Remember
that it creates a list item for every row in the
cursor but it only supports one item view type. That means
that all list items must use the same layout. If
we want today's forecast to look differently we're going to need
to create a custom CursorAdapter. That way we can have multiple
item view types. Then we can have different list item layouts
based on what row of the cursor we're looking at.
Note that the concept of item view types applies to
adapters in general, not just the CursorAdapter. If you open
up the documentation for CursorAdapter, you'll see that it's an abstract
class. It contains two abstract methods that you'll need to
override. The bindView method as well as the newView method.
The newView method knows how to return a new list
item layout, but doesn't contain data yet. The bindView method knows
how to take an existing layout and update
it with the data pointed to by the cursor